{
    "id": "2d4aa8598ac546b7854ea0877201b294",
    "title": "Sentence Completion",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "...................... Dalhousie is the cheapest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Of all hill stations",
                "From all hill stations"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He came to meet me …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in 5 o'clock",
                "on 5 o'clock",
                "at 5 o'clock"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is very good ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with drawing",
                "in drawing",
                "at drawing"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He shook ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hands with me",
                "my hand"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The train was moving .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in full speed",
                "on full speed",
                "at full speed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They were accused ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with theft",
                "of theft",
                "about theft"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no remedy …..................... .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with this illness",
                "for this illness",
                "to this illness"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no solution .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of this problem",
                "to this problem",
                "with this problem"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in poor health",
                "poor in health",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You must leave .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "within 5 o'clock",
                "before 5 o'clock",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}